We want to look at lists and list is something we all have to deal with in life.
You know what it's like.
We have lists and lists and we have lists about lists.
And uh, yep, we're going to buy the bread, the milk and the whatever that is the eggs.
So what is a list?
Well, obviously a list is simply an arrangement of items that have some link together.
Now, that doesn't necessarily mean they have to all be the same, like eggs and milk are not exactly
the same thing, but they all are part of a shopping list.
Or you may have a list of student marks or whatever it may be.
So it's some sort of arrangement.
And normally because they belong together, you want to work with them together.
So this is where lists are really important.
So rather than having separate variables.
So you want to have variables to store your student names.
You could have my name 12345.
But they're all names.
And they all to do with our students.
Maybe what would be better is if you could have them all in one list.
And so lists are a special space where you can store lots of things together that have some relation.
And so that's what we'll have a look at in this section is how you can create lists as a special variable
type, and then how you can work with lists, because they really do make life a lot easier as lists
do for us in normal life.
Let's see lists.